Tanaya Kanerkar

Nagpur, Maharashtra, India

kanerkartanaya29@gmail.com

8806531291

linkedin.com/in/tanaya-kanerkar-b29655288

Summary

I have experience in React JS, and Microsoft SQL Database (6 month) as well as I have a strong understanding of Redux hook and other state management libraries and its components, as well as HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript and other programming languages, I am a quick learner, excellent communication skills. Familiarity with (ES6, webpack, Git, GitHub etc.)

Experience



Frontend Developer

Qaswa Technologies Private Limited

Oct 2023 - Present (5 months)



SQL Developer

Ocean Software Technologies

Oct 2022 - Present (1 year 5 months)

I have work on Microsoft-SQL Database from Ocean Software Technologies Nagpur, I have experience about SQL serve, trigger, joins, Normalization, stored procedure, views etc. along with that i am worked on live project Agent Cash Collection Mobile App.

Education



Rashtrasant Tukadoji Maharaj Nagpur University, Nagpur

VMV College -Master of Computer Applications - MCA, Computer Programming Dec 2021 - Jul 2023



🥘 Shri Shivaji Science College

Bachelor's degree - CS, Computer Programming Jul 2018 - Jul 2021

Vidya Mandir Highschool and Junior College, Nagpur

HSC, 12th Jun 2016 - May 2018

Vidya Mandir High School Koradi, Nagpur

State Board of Maharashtra, 10th Jun 2015 - May 2016

Skills

Redux • Redux.js • Redux tool • HTML • Node.js • Git • HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • Microsoft SQL Server